Next time preview
So, what's going to happen with all the stuff on display? I guess you are wondering what is going to start,
We are going to make a song as a unit of the two of us!
The title is "Se-no!
Iyagi Hajjar!
Iyagi Hajjar means, "Let's talk.
Oh, let's talk.
That's the title of the song.
So this time, while talking about Iyagi Hajjar, we will talk about tanfull.
Strawberry candies and fruit candies are called tanful,
I would like to make tanful!
First of all, wipe off the water from the fruit with a stapler.
Remove the stems from the strawberries.
Oh, my job.
Shall we do it then?
Yes, please.
I feel like I'm being watched,
Sure.
I washed my hands.
Yes, I did.
Isn't it difficult? Cooking while talking.
You know, it's the first time I've ever done that.
Right.
I'm going to start cutting.
Then, leave it to me.
Oh, okay, oranges.
Mandarin oranges are very watery.
Okay.
Then, strawberries?
Yes, strawberry.
Oh, I made a mistake. I can't take it anymore.
It's okay, I like it. Because, you know,
Well, try alternating a little bit.
Yeah, it's important to think outside the box.
Oh! Good timing!
Excuse me! Excuse me!
Ta-da!
Thank you for your hard work!
Oh, that's right. We were talking about Cole, weren't we?
Oh, that's right.
I was wondering if you could do it.
I guess those of you who are familiar with Korea know what I'm talking about,
I think those of you who are familiar with Korea know that Korean callers say their names in the introduction,
I guess those who are familiar with Korea would know this.
If you are from Northeastern Japan, you would say,
If you are from Tohoku, you say something like "Hikari," "Hi," "Netsu," "Yuu," and so on,
Or "Ichi, a, ni, to, ha, ku, sa," and so on.
Cute.
Please take a look at the details.
Look at Korean idols.
I thought about having something like that,
But there were only two of them,
I thought it would be quick,
Is that okay? If you say it out loud,
I'll take care of it.
Okay, bye,
Furusame, Furusame,
I'll sing the lyrics with you,
I'll be happy any day.
Hindorayo.
Nam nam hingdalayo.
Nam Nam Nam Hindorayo.
Isn't she cute?
If you say it in a cute voice.
Hindoroyo.
Can I say it?
Hind royo.
Nam nam hing dre yo
Namnum hing dre yo.
Nam ne. I like it.
Really?
She says she's fine.
Hindorayo.
Oh, my God.
You want to hire me?
Let's hire one.
She says it's weird. She wants me to stop.
I don't know.
None of us do.
Even if I asked you to do this.
I don't know if they'd tell me.
They're totally acting like it.
Or they could be blue.
Or maybe you're a Shinju.
LOL
Hey.
Hindroyo.
Hindroyo
Hindollo yo.
There's more.
You want me to say OK?
That might be it.
But it's OK.
I don't mind.
So, I'm sure you all heard it because it was playing in the background music,
I hope you will listen to it while dancing with me and newcomer Hajime Yagi.
Thank you very much.
Bye-bye.
I've run out of pajamas, so you want to try one?
I want to try it!
Eat it!
Aaah!
I'll give you my first reaction later.
Well, I'm a little full anyway.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Okay.
Hmm?
Mmm!